<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<AboutUs>
    <Company>
        <Name>WestMed</Name>
        <Description>WestMed is the top e-commerce platform in the Philippines.</Description>
        <Founded>2018</Founded>
		
        <Mission>Our mission is to enhance the accessibility, affordability, and convenience of healthcare shopping, 
			ensuring that individuals and healthcare providers can easily find and purchase the medical supplies they need. 
			By leveraging cutting-edge technology and a customer-centric approach, WestMed aims to simplify the online shopping experience, 
			promote health and wellness, and contribute to the overall improvement of healthcare delivery in the Philippines.</Mission>
			
        <PrimaryGoal>The primary goal of WestMed is to become the leading healthcare e-commerce platform in the Philippines
		by offering a seamless, secure, and efficient online shopping experience. 
		We aim to ensure that customers have easy access to a diverse range of high-quality medical products and services, 
		backed by robust customer support and reliable fulfillment processes.
		Through continuous innovation and a commitment to excellence, 
		WestMed strives to improve the overall shopping experience and contribute to the betterment of healthcare access and delivery in the region.</PrimaryGoal>
		
    </Company>
    <Sections>
        <Section title="Our Purpose">
            <Content>The purpose of WestMed is to revolutionize the healthcare e-commerce landscape by providing a comprehensive, 
			user-friendly platform that connects customers with high-quality medical products and services. 
			</Content>
        </Section>
        <Section title="Our Positioning">
            <Content>WestMed positions itself as the leading healthcare e-commerce platform in the Philippines, 
			dedicated to providing an unparalleled shopping experience for medical supplies and health products. 
			We aim to be the trusted partner for individuals, healthcare providers, 
			and institutions by offering a comprehensive selection of quality products, competitive pricing, and exceptional customer service.</Content>
        </Section>
        <Section title="Customer Care">
            <Links>
                <Link>
                    <Title>Contact Us</Title>
                    <URL>http://localhost/WestMed/contact.html</URL>
                </Link>
                <Link>
                    <Title>Payment Method</Title>
                    <URL>http://localhost/WestMed/payment.html</URL>
                </Link>
                <Link>
                    <Title>Help Centre</Title>
                    <URL>http://localhost/WestMed/help.html</URL>
                </Link>
            </Links>
        </Section>
        <Section title="About WestMed">
            <Links>
                <Link>
                    <Title>About Us</Title>
                    <URL>http://localhost/WestMed/about.html</URL>
                </Link>
                <Link>
                    <Title>WestMed</Title>
                    <URL>http://localhost/WestMed/shopper.html</URL>
                </Link>
                <Link>
                    <Title>WestMed Careers</Title>
                    <URL>http://localhost/WestMed/careers.html</URL>
                </Link>
            </Links>
        </Section>
        <Section title="Find Us On">
            <SocialMedia>
                <Platform>
                    <Name>Facebook</Name>
                    <URL>http://facebook.com/westmed</URL>
                </Platform>
                <Platform>
                    <Name>Instagram</Name>
                    <URL>http://instagram.com/westmed</URL>
                </Platform>
                <Platform>
                    <Name>Twitter</Name>
                    <URL>http://twitter.com/westmed</URL>
                </Platform>
            </SocialMedia>
        </Section>
        <Section title="Payment">
            <Methods>
                <Method>PayPal</Method>
                <Method>VISA</Method>
                <Method>GCash</Method>
                <Method>PayMaya</Method>
            </Methods>
        </Section>
    </Sections>
    <Footer>
        <Copyright>2023 © WestMed</Copyright>
    </Footer>
</AboutUs>
